some animal rescue news out of New York
officers saved a bald eagle trapped in a
reservoir oh great another Eagle saved
by man honestly what's the obsession
with the Eagle it's supposed to be a
symbol of freedom but the Nazis the
Nazis love the Eagle the NRA
okay the Eagle the guns he's already a
killing machine on his own do you know
how many tax dollars we spend on bald
eagles
they're not even endangered anymore but
they still protected by multiple federal
laws their welfare birds sucking on the
government's teat America needs a new
bird to represent the country one that's
pulled itself up by its bootstraps the
pigeon the pigeons were messages during
World War one and World War two and
probably other Wars pigeons were even
used as spies that's a real photo the
real photo they weren't great spies but
they were the best spies they could be
the pigeon is an American war hero and
just like our human bets our bird
veterans are out on the street begging
for bread crumbs walk past like they're
not even there called horrible names
like rats with wings next time you see a
pigeon you thank them for their service
tonight I salute you pigeons whether
you're a homing racing fantail English
powder parlor Ola bohemian or the basic
domestic
you're a hero to the pigeon my men
finally embrace your wonder and drink
you the way you've always deserved to be
treated be free pigeon be free by you
know mr. Birds
[Music]